let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "Fortschreiten", "answer": "to progress", "options": ["to employ, to engage", "to explain", "demonstrate, pradarshisu", "to progress"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "beschreiben", "answer": "to describe", "options": ["to accept", "refuse, tiraskarisu, niraakarisu", "to describe", "to lead, netrutva vahisu"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "bedrohen", "answer": "threaten, bedarisu, hedarisu", "options": ["to employ, to engage", "restore, marunirmaana madu", "impose, hEru", "threaten, bedarisu, hedarisu"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "streiten", "answer": "to fight", "options": ["to correspond,", "to cheat, mosa madu, vanchisu", "to fight", "to contain, to comprise, kannada : OLagollu"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "ansehen", "answer": "to view, nodu", "options": ["to accept", "to measure, aLeyu", "to view, nodu", "to require"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "\ufeffbeachten", "answer": "gamanisu , to note, to observe", "options": ["to defeat, solu vante maadu", "to describe", "gamanisu , to note, to observe", "to waste, vyartha madu"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "niederschlagen", "answer": "to defeat, solu vante maadu", "options": ["to defeat, solu vante maadu", "to cheat, mosa madu, vanchisu", "to explain", "also to convert but with maths, dollar to euro, miles to Kilometer etc."]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "erzeugen", "answer": "create", "options": ["to report, varadi madu", "create", "use, baLasu", "to employ, to engage"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "verlassen", "answer": "leave, bittu bidu", "options": ["BaLasu, upayogisu", "to cheat, mosa madu, vanchisu", "to edit, to process usually textual content", "leave, bittu bidu"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "betonen", "answer": "ottu kodu, emphasize", "options": ["ottu kodu, emphasize", "to console, samadhanapadisu", "lekka haaku, to count, calculate", "to consider, to look into"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "enthalten", "answer": "to contain, to comprise, kannada : OLagollu", "options": ["to console, samadhanapadisu", "demonstrate, pradarshisu", "arthaisu, to mean", "to contain, to comprise, kannada : OLagollu"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "ableiten", "answer": "deflect, haLLa hidi", "options": ["to approve, to permit", "to suffer, baLalu", "deflect, haLLa hidi", "to report, varadi madu"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "bemessen", "answer": "to measure, aLeyu", "options": ["to suffer, baLalu", "to measure, aLeyu", "threaten, bedarisu, hedarisu", "to pose,"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "mitteilen", "answer": "to inform, maahiti kodu", "options": ["to inform, maahiti kodu", "to consider, to look into", "impose, hEru", "consume, Kannada: Sevisu"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "anschauen", "answer": "to view, nodu", "options": ["to view, nodu", "to involve, to take part,", "restore, marunirmaana madu", "to pose,"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "beeinflussen", "answer": "influence", "options": ["also to convert but with maths, dollar to euro, miles to Kilometer etc.", "to accept", "arthaisu, to mean", "influence"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "ersetzen", "answer": "replace", "options": ["gamanisu , to note, to observe", "specify, nirdistapadisu", "to accept", "replace"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "empfinden", "answer": "to feel", "options": ["ottu kodu, emphasize", "to adjust", "demonstrate, pradarshisu", "to feel"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "specifizieren", "answer": "specify, nirdistapadisu", "options": ["attack, daaLi madu", "pramaanikarisu, dhrudikarisu", "to describe", "specify, nirdistapadisu"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "genehmigen", "answer": "to approve, to permit", "options": ["to bless, aashirvadisu", "to approve, to permit", "to pose,", "to accept"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "verwenden", "answer": "BaLasu, upayogisu", "options": ["to prove", "BaLasu, upayogisu", "to hate, Dweshisu", "to employ, to engage"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "entsprechen", "answer": "to correspond,", "options": ["to correspond,", "use, baLasu", "to explain", "to convert, religion, Konvertierung    Noun"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "verbrauchen", "answer": "consume, Kannada: Sevisu", "options": ["consume, Kannada: Sevisu", "to renew, naveekarisu", "to edit, to process usually textual content", "to correspond,"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "Verhindern", "answer": "to prevent", "options": ["to convert, religion, Konvertierung    Noun", "to measure, aLeyu", "to prevent", "to contain, to comprise, kannada : OLagollu"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "wiederherstellen", "answer": "restore, marunirmaana madu", "options": ["restore, marunirmaana madu", "appear", "job apply", "to bless, aashirvadisu"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "jdn_tr\u00f6sten", "answer": "to console, samadhanapadisu", "options": ["to take measure, kaigoLLu", "to apply  Anwayisu, Apply, to use", "to console, samadhanapadisu", "to view, nodu mattu pareekshisu"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "argumentieren", "answer": "to argue", "options": ["to argue", "to riot, galabhe madu", "protest, pratibhatisu", "abuse, DurbaLake madu"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "erl\u00e4utern", "answer": "to explain", "options": ["combine, join", "gamanisu , to note, to observe", "protest, pratibhatisu", "to explain"]}, {"numb": 29, "question": "protestieren", "answer": "protest, pratibhatisu", "options": ["to fight", "to rectify, saripadisu", "to prohibit", "protest, pratibhatisu"]}, {"numb": 30, "question": "besichtigen", "answer": "to view, nodu mattu pareekshisu", "options": ["to report, varadi madu", "to view, nodu mattu pareekshisu", "also to convert but with maths, dollar to euro, miles to Kilometer etc.", "to damage, haani madu"]}, {"numb": 31, "question": "segnen", "answer": "to bless, aashirvadisu", "options": ["to damage, haani madu", "deflect, haLLa hidi", "refuse, tiraskarisu, niraakarisu", "to bless, aashirvadisu"]}, {"numb": 32, "question": "Abnutzen", "answer": "abuse, DurbaLake madu", "options": ["to feel", "to quit, tyajisu", "abuse, DurbaLake madu", "to last"]}, {"numb": 33, "question": "randalieren", "answer": "to riot, galabhe madu", "options": ["attack, daaLi madu", "to apply  Anwayisu, Apply, to use", "to riot, galabhe madu", "influence"]}, {"numb": 34, "question": "nutzen", "answer": "use, baLasu", "options": ["use, baLasu", "to require", "translate", "to report, varadi madu"]}, {"numb": 35, "question": "hassen", "answer": "to hate, Dweshisu", "options": ["to hate, Dweshisu", "to require", "to act, vartisu", "to rectify, saripadisu"]}, {"numb": 36, "question": "verwunden", "answer": "to get wound, gaayagonda", "options": ["to get wound, gaayagonda", "to update,", "to accept", "use, baLasu"]}, {"numb": 37, "question": "\u00fcbersehen", "answer": "overlook, kadegaNisu", "options": ["use, baLasu", "to require", "to get wound, gaayagonda", "overlook, kadegaNisu"]}, {"numb": 38, "question": "leiden", "answer": "to suffer, baLalu", "options": ["combine, join", "to suffer, baLalu", "consume, Kannada: Sevisu", "create"]}, {"numb": 39, "question": "annehmen", "answer": "to accept", "options": ["to rectify, saripadisu", "to accept", "to report, varadi madu", "to console, samadhanapadisu"]}, {"numb": 40, "question": "darstellen", "answer": "to pose,", "options": ["to pose,", "to argue", "BaLasu, upayogisu", "to require"]}, {"numb": 41, "question": "beglaubigen", "answer": "pramaanikarisu, dhrudikarisu", "options": ["to describe", "take serious, Gambhiravagi parigaNisu", "to describe", "pramaanikarisu, dhrudikarisu"]}, {"numb": 42, "question": "aktualisieren", "answer": "to update,", "options": ["to loot, looti hode", "use, baLasu", "to rectify, saripadisu", "to update,"]}, {"numb": 43, "question": "erzaehlen", "answer": "to describe", "options": ["to describe", "attack, daaLi madu", "revoke, vapasur kare, raddumadu", "to damage, haani madu"]}, {"numb": 44, "question": "benutzen", "answer": "use, baLasu", "options": ["to involve, to take part,", "use, baLasu", "to take measure, kaigoLLu", "use, kannada: BaLasu"]}, {"numb": 45, "question": "korrigieren", "answer": "to rectify, saripadisu", "options": ["consider", "grab, grasp, hididuko", "to rectify, saripadisu", "to view, nodu mattu pareekshisu"]}, {"numb": 46, "question": "meinen", "answer": "to mean,", "options": ["to accept", "to progress", "to mean,", "to torture, chitrahimse kodu"]}, {"numb": 47, "question": "Kombinieren", "answer": "combine, join", "options": ["combine, join", "to waste, vyartha madu", "to accept", "to approve, to permit"]}, {"numb": 48, "question": "widersprechen", "answer": "to object, prashnisu,", "options": ["to react, pratikrayisu", "protest, pratibhatisu", "to object, prashnisu,", "consider"]}, {"numb": 49, "question": "bewerben", "answer": "job apply", "options": ["consider", "to feel", "job apply", "to argue"]}, {"numb": 50, "question": "bitten", "answer": "to request appeal, manavi madu", "options": ["to match, hondisu", "to view, nodu", "to request appeal, manavi madu", "refrain, kannada: dooraviru"]}, {"numb": 51, "question": "umrechnen", "answer": "also to convert but with maths, dollar to euro, miles to Kilometer etc.", "options": ["also to convert but with maths, dollar to euro, miles to Kilometer etc.", "hurry up", "to convince", "deflect, haLLa hidi"]}, {"numb": 52, "question": "sch\u00e4digen", "answer": "to damage, haani madu", "options": ["to accept", "to loot, looti hode", "to damage, haani madu", "to view, nodu"]}, {"numb": 53, "question": "Konvertieren", "answer": "to convert, religion, Konvertierung    Noun", "options": ["lekka haaku, to count, calculate", "grab, grasp, hididuko", "to convert, religion, Konvertierung    Noun", "to progress"]}, {"numb": 54, "question": "agieren", "answer": "to act, vartisu", "options": ["to act, vartisu", "to react, pratikrayisu", "to damage, haani madu", "hurry up"]}, {"numb": 55, "question": "anklagen", "answer": "to accuse, aaropa maadu, aapadisu", "options": ["to request appeal, manavi madu", "grab, grasp, hididuko", "to update,", "to accuse, aaropa maadu, aapadisu"]}, {"numb": 56, "question": "herstellen", "answer": "manufacture, tayarisu", "options": ["to damage, haani madu", "to prevent", "threaten, bedarisu, hedarisu", "manufacture, tayarisu"]}, {"numb": 57, "question": "verboten", "answer": "to prohibit", "options": ["to describe", "specify, nirdistapadisu", "to prohibit", "to view, nodu"]}, {"numb": 58, "question": "auferlegen", "answer": "impose, hEru", "options": ["to damage, haani madu", "impose, hEru", "to last", "to involve, to take part,"]}, {"numb": 59, "question": "besch\u00e4ftigen", "answer": "to employ, to engage", "options": ["to employ, to engage", "to require", "overlook, kadegaNisu", "to explain"]}, {"numb": 60, "question": "verbessern", "answer": "to improve", "options": ["to improve", "to damage, haani madu", "to update,", "abuse, DurbaLake madu"]}, {"numb": 61, "question": "bezeugen", "answer": "witness, saakshiyagu", "options": ["to describe", "to pose,", "witness, saakshiyagu", "to fight"]}, {"numb": 62, "question": "reagieren", "answer": "to react, pratikrayisu", "options": ["to lead, netrutva vahisu", "to react, pratikrayisu", "pramaanikarisu, dhrudikarisu", "to receive"]}, {"numb": 63, "question": "greifen", "answer": "grab, grasp, hididuko", "options": ["deflect, haLLa hidi", "grab, grasp, hididuko", "to quit, tyajisu", "to riot, galabhe madu"]}, {"numb": 64, "question": "bedeuten", "answer": "arthaisu, to mean", "options": ["combine, join", "to feel", "to view, nodu mattu pareekshisu", "arthaisu, to mean"]}, {"numb": 65, "question": "erscheinen", "answer": "appear", "options": ["appear", "to accuse, aaropa maadu, aapadisu", "to act, vartisu", "to contradict, virodhabhasavgi helu"]}, {"numb": 66, "question": "Verwenden", "answer": "use, kannada: BaLasu", "options": ["specify, nirdistapadisu", "create", "use, kannada: BaLasu", "to object, prashnisu,"]}, {"numb": 67, "question": "verschwunden", "answer": "disappear, missing,  kanmareyaagu", "options": ["ottu kodu, emphasize", "to progress", "disappear, missing,  kanmareyaagu", "to argue"]}, {"numb": 68, "question": "empf\u00e4gen", "answer": "to receive", "options": ["to describe", "to receive", "to damage, haani madu", "to prohibit"]}, {"numb": 69, "question": "wiederspiegeln", "answer": "to reflect", "options": ["to prove", "to involve, to take part,", "to rectify, saripadisu", "to reflect"]}, {"numb": 70, "question": "Ernst nehmen", "answer": "take serious, Gambhiravagi parigaNisu", "options": ["take serious, Gambhiravagi parigaNisu", "to view, nodu", "to get wound, gaayagonda", "leave, bittu bidu"]}, {"numb": 71, "question": "anpassen", "answer": "to adjust", "options": ["to adjust", "to feel", "to react, pratikrayisu", "ottu kodu, emphasize"]}, {"numb": 72, "question": "erfordern", "answer": "to require", "options": ["to employ, to engage", "overlook, kadegaNisu", "to improve", "to require"]}, {"numb": 73, "question": "interpretieren", "answer": "to interpret, arthaisikollu", "options": ["to bless, aashirvadisu", "to progress", "to interpret, arthaisikollu", "translate"]}, {"numb": 74, "question": "besch\u00e4digen", "answer": "to damage, haani madu", "options": ["to accept", "to damage, haani madu", "to improve", "BaLasu, upayogisu"]}, {"numb": 75, "question": "fuehlen sich", "answer": "to feel", "options": ["to view, nodu", "to feel", "consider", "to progress"]}, {"numb": 76, "question": "Anwenden", "answer": "to apply  Anwayisu, Apply, to use", "options": ["to apply  Anwayisu, Apply, to use", "influence", "specify, nirdistapadisu", "to feel"]}, {"numb": 77, "question": "demonstrieren", "answer": "demonstrate, pradarshisu", "options": ["demonstrate, pradarshisu", "to prove", "to adjust", "arthaisu, to mean"]}, {"numb": 78, "question": "ergreifen", "answer": "to take measure, kaigoLLu", "options": ["to take measure, kaigoLLu", "to prohibit", "to fight", "specify, nirdistapadisu"]}, {"numb": 79, "question": "akzeptieren", "answer": "to accept", "options": ["to describe", "to accept", "to approve, to permit", "leave, bittu bidu"]}, {"numb": 80, "question": "bekommen", "answer": "to receive", "options": ["to receive", "to rectify, saripadisu", "to suffer, baLalu", "to damage, haani madu"]}, {"numb": 81, "question": "bearbeiten", "answer": "to edit, to process usually textual content", "options": ["to edit, to process usually textual content", "to hate, Dweshisu", "to fight", "to require"]}, {"numb": 82, "question": "beweisen", "answer": "to prove", "options": ["to prove", "to prevent", "impose, hEru", "to accuse, aaropa maadu, aapadisu"]}, {"numb": 83, "question": "erneuen", "answer": "to renew, naveekarisu", "options": ["to view, nodu mattu pareekshisu", "to renew, naveekarisu", "to adjust", "translate"]}, {"numb": 84, "question": "ber\u00fccksichtigen", "answer": "consider", "options": ["to explain", "to convert, religion, Konvertierung    Noun", "consider", "specify, nirdistapadisu"]}, {"numb": 85, "question": "widerrufen", "answer": "revoke, vapasur kare, raddumadu", "options": ["revoke, vapasur kare, raddumadu", "to update,", "refuse, tiraskarisu, niraakarisu", "to measure, aLeyu"]}, {"numb": 86, "question": "dauern", "answer": "to last", "options": ["manufacture, tayarisu", "to view, nodu mattu pareekshisu", "refuse, tiraskarisu, niraakarisu", "to last"]}, {"numb": 87, "question": "verschwenden", "answer": "to waste, vyartha madu", "options": ["to explain", "to explain", "to waste, vyartha madu", "disappear, missing,  kanmareyaagu"]}, {"numb": 88, "question": "erklaeren", "answer": "to explain", "options": ["to explain", "to take measure, kaigoLLu", "to update,", "to act, vartisu"]}, {"numb": 89, "question": "zur\u00fcckhalten", "answer": "refrain, kannada: dooraviru", "options": ["to contain, to comprise, kannada : OLagollu", "refrain, kannada: dooraviru", "to object, prashnisu,", "to rectify, saripadisu"]}, {"numb": 90, "question": "berichten", "answer": "to report, varadi madu", "options": ["to report, varadi madu", "deflect, haLLa hidi", "to renew, naveekarisu", "to object, prashnisu,"]}, {"numb": 91, "question": "schildern", "answer": "to describe", "options": ["to hate, Dweshisu", "to describe", "create", "to involve, to take part,"]}, {"numb": 92, "question": "ben\u00f6tigen", "answer": "to require", "options": ["to take measure, kaigoLLu", "arthaisu, to mean", "to require", "to explain"]}, {"numb": 93, "question": "jdn_\u00fcberzeugen", "answer": "to convince", "options": ["to report, varadi madu", "to convince", "to defeat, solu vante maadu", "to console, samadhanapadisu"]}, {"numb": 94, "question": "verzichten", "answer": "to quit, tyajisu", "options": ["to describe", "to quit, tyajisu", "to receive", "to suffer, baLalu"]}, {"numb": 95, "question": "qu\u00e4len", "answer": "to torture, chitrahimse kodu", "options": ["to torture, chitrahimse kodu", "to get wound, gaayagonda", "witness, saakshiyagu", "lekka haaku, to count, calculate"]}, {"numb": 96, "question": "beheben", "answer": "to rectify, saripadisu", "options": ["to describe", "to damage, haani madu", "to explain", "to rectify, saripadisu"]}, {"numb": 97, "question": "betrachten", "answer": "to consider, to look into", "options": ["to consider, to look into", "to describe", "gamanisu , to note, to observe", "to describe"]}, {"numb": 98, "question": "beeilen", "answer": "hurry up", "options": ["to renew, naveekarisu", "to rectify, saripadisu", "to apply  Anwayisu, Apply, to use", "hurry up"]}, {"numb": 99, "question": "verletzen", "answer": "injure, novuntu madu, gaya madu", "options": ["to view, nodu", "to explain", "to view, nodu", "injure, novuntu madu, gaya madu"]}, {"numb": 100, "question": "betr\u00fcgen", "answer": "to cheat, mosa madu, vanchisu", "options": ["refrain, kannada: dooraviru", "pramaanikarisu, dhrudikarisu", "to cheat, mosa madu, vanchisu", "to convert, religion, Konvertierung    Noun"]}, {"numb": 101, "question": "widerreden", "answer": "to contradict, virodhabhasavgi helu", "options": ["to contradict, virodhabhasavgi helu", "consider", "to view, nodu mattu pareekshisu", "grab, grasp, hididuko"]}, {"numb": 102, "question": "zuordnen", "answer": "to match, hondisu", "options": ["to match, hondisu", "to view, nodu", "create", "job apply"]}, {"numb": 103, "question": "brauchen", "answer": "to require", "options": ["gamanisu , to note, to observe", "manufacture, tayarisu", "to improve", "to require"]}, {"numb": 104, "question": "\u00fcbersetzen", "answer": "translate", "options": ["attack, daaLi madu", "translate", "to approve, to permit", "to correspond,"]}, {"numb": 105, "question": "leiten", "answer": "to lead, netrutva vahisu", "options": ["to lead, netrutva vahisu", "to request appeal, manavi madu", "demonstrate, pradarshisu", "to suffer, baLalu"]}, {"numb": 106, "question": "widerlegen", "answer": "refuse, tiraskarisu, niraakarisu", "options": ["deflect, haLLa hidi", "specify, nirdistapadisu", "to fight", "refuse, tiraskarisu, niraakarisu"]}, {"numb": 107, "question": "rechnen", "answer": "lekka haaku, to count, calculate", "options": ["lekka haaku, to count, calculate", "refrain, kannada: dooraviru", "to measure, aLeyu", "ottu kodu, emphasize"]}, {"numb": 108, "question": "beteiligen", "answer": "to involve, to take part,", "options": ["to edit, to process usually textual content", "to involve, to take part,", "injure, novuntu madu, gaya madu", "to convince"]}, {"numb": 109, "question": "angreifen", "answer": "attack, daaLi madu", "options": ["to convince", "attack, daaLi madu", "combine, join", "to console, samadhanapadisu"]}, {"numb": 110, "question": "messen", "answer": "to measure, aLeyu", "options": ["to contain, to comprise, kannada : OLagollu", "to measure, aLeyu", "overlook, kadegaNisu", "to feel"]}, {"numb": 111, "question": "rauben", "answer": "to loot, looti hode", "options": ["to damage, haani madu", "to loot, looti hode", "to describe", "to explain"]}];